---
---

data = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'On the TV sitcom The Munsters, what was Lily Munsters maiden name?',
      answers: [
        'Ponduke',
        'Spinehedge',
        'Dracula',
        'Cruella',
        'Madriga'
      ],
      correct: 2
    },
    {
      question: 'What foreign government contributed the greatest amount of money for the relief of victims of the 1906 San Francisco earthquake?',
      answers: [
        'China',
        'Luxembourg',
        'Japan',
        'Russia',
        'Canada'
      ],
      correct: 2
    },

    {
      question: 'Which is the only U.S. state to produce coffee?',
      answers: [
        "Missouri",
        "Alaska",
        "Illinois",
        "Hawaii",
        "New York"
      ],
      correct: 3
    },

    {
      question: 'What famous actress once said, "The less I behave like Whistlers mother the night before, the more I look like her the morning after"?',
      answers: [
        "Tallulah Bankhead",
        "Hayley Mills",
        "Shirley Temple",
        "Gladys George",
        "Helen Hayes"
      ],
      correct: 0
    },

    {
      question: 'Whose appearance in a nearly transparent white fishnet bathing suit in the 1978 Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue led an editor to promise, "We never have, and never will, run anything so revealing again?"',
      answers: [
        "Michaela Kocianova",
        "Jessica Gomes",
        "Alina Puscau",
        "Ana Beatriz Barros",
        "Cheryl Tiegs"
      ],
      correct: 3
    },

    {
      question: 'The name of what American state capital means "sheltered harbor"?',
      answers: [
        "Albany",
        "Honolulu",
        "Tallahassee",
        "Raleigh",
        "Columbia"
      ],
      correct: 1
    },

    {
      question: 'When the bald eagle was first named, what was the meaning of the word "bald?',
      answers: [
        "regal",
        "strong",
        "feathered",
        "white",
        "hairless"
      ],
      correct: 3
    },

    {
      question: 'What two cities were linked by the Orient Express?',
      answers: [
        "Brussels and Damascus",
        "Ankara and Athens",
        "Pyongyang and Seoul",
        "Beijing and Tokyo",
        "Paris and Istanbul"
      ],
      correct: 4
    },

    {
      question: 'In England, whats a "bap"?',
      answers: [
        "a hamburger bun",
        "a gallon of water",
        "a bouquet of flowers",
        "a banana peel",
        "a toothbrush holder"
      ],
      correct: 0
    },

    {
      question: 'How many sides are there to a snow crystal?',
      answers: [
        "Three",
        "Four",
        "Six",
        "Eight",
        "Sixteen"
      ],
      correct: 2
    },

    {
      question: 'What are the only two letters that are not on a telphone dial?',
      answers: [
        "M and P",
        "D and Q",
        "Q and Z",
        "H and R",
        "I and J"
      ],
      correct: 2
    },

    {
      question: 'Together, baseball-playing brothers Hank and Tommy Aaron hit 768 home runs. How many were Tommys?',
      answers: [
        "668",
        "7",
        "357",
        "13",
        "49"
      ],
      correct: 3
    },

    {
      question: 'What capital is the oldest continuously inhabited city in the world?',
      answers: [
        "Brasilia, Brazil",
        "Ankara, Turkey",
        "Damascus, Syria",
        "Paris, France",
        "Moscow, Russia"
      ],
      correct: 2
    },

    {
      question: 'What French city was home to Anthelme Brillat-Savarin, the famous gastronome?',
      answers: [
        "Lille",
        "Normandy",
        "Marseilles",
        "Belley",
        "Paris"
      ],
      correct: 3
    },

    {
      question: 'What is philematology?',
      answers: [
        "The science of animal feces",
        "The science of kissing",
        "The science of sex",
        "The science of architecture",
        "The science of shopping"
      ],
      correct: 1
    },

    {
      question: 'What is a "tittle"?',
      answers: [
        "The dot over the letters 'i' and 'j'",
        "A cucumber seed",
        "A tiny hair found on the body of an insect",
        "A section of a sandwich cut into 15 pieces",
        "A stitch mark on a football"
      ],
      correct: 0
    },

    {
      question: 'What percentage of the worlds food crops are pollinated by insects?',
      answers: [
        "50 percent",
        "60 percent",
        "70 percent",
        "80 percent",
        "90 percent"
      ],
      correct: 3
    },

    {
      question: 'What fruit did early Greek Olympians eat for their health and sometimes even wear as medals?',
      answers: [
        "grapes",
        "figs",
        "pomegranates",
        "olives",
        "pears"
      ],
      correct: 1 
    },

    {
      question: 'What was the average yearly salary of an American public school teacher at the turn of the 20th century?',
      answers: [
        "$445",
        "$1,050",
        "$325",
        "$4,300",
        "$110"
      ],
      correct: 2
    },

    {
      question: 'What was the name of the daughter Lady Emma Hamilton bore Admiral Horatio Nelson?',
      answers: [
        "Hamiltonia",
        "Emma",
        "Norma",
        "Horatia",
        "Admiralia"
      ],
      correct: 3
    }
  ]
}



